

PROFILE

User Experience Designer, who loves building Web, iPad & Mobile solutions & have designed features & flows for various products (requirement gathering to prototyping). Also designed digital media kits (brand websites, logos, banners, etc.) for both online and offline advertising.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+91-9131991448

WFBSITE:

https://purvakushwaha.github.io

EMAIL:

purva.kushwaha99@gmail.com

DRIBBLE:

https://dribbble.com/purva_kushwaha

LINKEDLN:

https://linkedin.com/in/purva-kushwaha-5885aa118/

SKILLS

- Sketch
- Adobe: XD, Photoshop, Illustrator
- Figma
- Marvel App
- Zeplin
- HTML/CSS

HOBBIES

- Table Tennis
- Reading
- Travelling

PURVA K KUSHWAHA

UX Designer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancing - Independent Designer

June, 2020 – Present

Worked with many companies and startups and help them design their **Media Kits**, **Online/Offline marketing elements** from logos, browser, visiting and invitation cards to websites, mobile application screens.

Paragon Business Solutions Pvt. Ltd. - UX Designer (Digivalet & CasaDigi) May 2019 – June 2020

Digivalet is the world's first touch-based guest room experience solution whereas **CasaDigi** is for luxurious homes. Here, experienced in designing user interactive features like **Food & Beverages**, **Chatbot**, etc. and worked on many internal projects like revamping **Digivalet Dashboard**, **CasaDigi Studio**, etc.

EngineerBabu Pvt. Ltd. - Graphic Designer Intern

March 2018 - July 2018

During internship, experienced creating various **advertising elements** like Logos, hiring posters, t-shirts, cups, laptop stickers.

Indore Technical Community & Microsoft Student Partner

2017 - 2019

Visited BITs Pilani Summit, Rajasthan Hackathon 5.0 and joining communities like Google Developers Group, Facebook Developers Circle, GirlScript and Women Techmakers, Indore. Also worked as Student Ambassador at Skillenza, Progate, Internshala (8.0, 9.0 and 12.0).

Other Internships

- Affimantus Technologies, Indore (Website Development)
- L&T Electrical & Automation, Indore (IOT & Product Development Phases)
- Nuclear Power Corporations of India Ltd. (TAPS) Setup of PPPoE Authentication Sever Development Phases

EDUCATION

Indore Institute of Science & Technology, Indore, MP

2015-2019

Coordinated and organized many events like **Techfest** & Technical events of **Microsoft**, **Facebook** and anchored at cultural events like Concerts, Annual Day, Kavi-Sammelan, etc.

- Awarded as **Star Achiever** in my Final Year.
- Won Madhya Pradesh **States**, Table Tennis, 2015.
- AICTE Conference, Japan had selected the Research paper RNN Based Music Generation
- Major project was **Smart Dustbin with GPS service** using IOT & Rasberry Pi.
- Minor project was **BookFood** Website, a website for user and caters.

Atomic Energy Central School No.1, Tarapur, Dist. Palghar, MH

2002 - 2015

Positioned as Head Girl and twice severed as House Caption.

Won many co-curricular activities (Debates, Quizzes, Paper presentations to Group Dance, Group Singing, etc.) and various sports events.